<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel Keyes</title>
    <link>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daniel Keyes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 10:26:44 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.danielkeyes.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 10:26:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Current Android developer for a financial institution.
Experience I have eight years of experience doing software development with the previous three years primarily doing native Android development. I currently work primarily in Kotlin as well as Java.
Education Masters in Computer Science, Texas State University, 2012
Bachelors in Computer Science, Texas State University, 2008
Personal Currently I live in San Antonio Texas with my wife and our three rescue dogs. I am a Texas native but will always have a special place in my heart for Colorado which I visit frequently with my wife for the beautiful scenery and spectacular trails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Reveal - Android App</title>
      <link>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/thereveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.danielkeyes.dev/thereveal/</guid>
      <description>View Your Reveal To view your reveal, please download the app, The Reveal, from the Android App store and paste your code into the reveal block and hit the reveal button.
If you have the app installed, you can also click the shared reveal link from your Android device to load the reveal directly into the app.
About The Reveal I created this app as a way to do the birth reveal for my brother who is also an Android developer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
